The most terrifying images are the ones that are real.
Shutter is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Masayuki Ochiai.
A newly married couple discovers disturbing, ghostly images in
photographs they develop after a tragic accident.
Fearing the manifestations may be connected, they investigate and
learn that some mysteries are better left unsolved.
Benjamin Shaw, played by Joshua Jackson.
Jane Shaw, played by Rachael Taylor.
Megumi Tanaka, played by Megumi Okina.
Bruno, played by David Denman.
Yoko, played by Elly Otoguro.
Adam, played by John Hensley.
Shutter is a 2008 American supernatural horror film directed by
Masayuki Ochiai and distributed by 20th Century Fox.
It was written by Luke Dawson and is a remake of
the 2004 Thai film of the same name.
Its story follows newlywed couple Ben and Jane who have just
moved to Japan for a promising job opportunity.
After a tragic car accident that leads to the death of a young girl, Ben begins noticing strange blurs in many of
his fashion shoot photographs, which Jane suspects is the spirit of the dead girl that they killed.
The film stars Joshua Jackson, Rachael Taylor, and Megumi Okina.
It was produced by Regency Enterprises and was released on March 21, 2008.
It grossed $10.4 million in its opening weekend and $48 million worldwide, against an $8 million
budget, making the film a box office success, but was negatively received from critics.
The film explores themes of suicide, japan,
nightmare, photographer, photography.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.